{
    "id": "f417c78dbe2540c49300beded49dc6a3",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The turban and the beard easily distinguish a Sikh ——————— others.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4c827c5c63754dda9fac94877f4ee201"
        },
        {
            "question": "The laboratory should be furnished ———————- all necessary equipment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c69c47dde4af41fa964872aa95b57a15"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is keen ———————- building a career in music.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "1f41235144544821893778f9e5c4ca3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a disgrace ——————- her family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "32f107b62bb54dd6a74dca89fac5c78f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was the first to alight ——————- the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "down",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "032447918c8e4ca2bbcc80f35ddc78fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is busy ——————– his studies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "332ef426bda846e3b769fda1c2a1595e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is addicted ——————– drugs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "from",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "d3a86782826048ed8c5543620d55b0d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hotel is adjacent ——————- the railway station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94401e939081495b8d3f10b95f6b49d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "During his speech, he alluded ——————– a story in the Vedas.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d78526ed06b849cc99d8b9450b5c0f8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must apologize ——————— him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7210839273a542acb8990c246f7796b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The inspector commented favorably ——————– our work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ff2747e038e64c1c8bd433fec5ec0709"
        },
        {
            "question": "I congratulated him —————— his success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "with",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc3bc8501a1245bfbeabcd9f486bbdd6"
        }
    ]
}